dezinehub.com 2005-04-03

# Ready to use PSD Templates | Website Templates | Logo Templates

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. When a user submits personal information, it is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the general public. This prevents any malicious use of your information. All financial information that is submitted to our site is encrypted and is stored on private server space that is not accessible to the general public. Further, users can select to transmit order information over a secure connection, which increases the security of each transaction.  
**  
** **Credit card Transactions**   
All Credit Card payments on our site are processed through 2checkout.com merchant services. Creditcard information collected by 2checkout.com is stored only at 2checkout.com.  
**  
Site Registration**  
Registration process requires users to submit contact information. This data is used to identify the customer when logged-in into the system as well as for invoicing purposes. Your contact information may be used to contact you. If the customer is interested, then he/she will be receiving information promotional material. If selected, this feature may be turned off at any time. Our company will not sell or give client list to any other party. 

**IP Addresses and Logging**  
Our server logs information regarding visitors to our site, such as IP address, date/time, and pages accessed. This information is solely used to generate reports for statistical purposes. 

**IP Addresses and Cookies**   
We use your computer's IP (Internet Protocol) address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your time spent at our sites, and to gather broad demographic information. This allows us to see which parts of our sites our users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means, for instance, that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will remain anonymous. 

**Profile Update**  
When logged in, you can change your customer information in your member area at anytime. 

**Our Privacy Philosophy**  
DezineHub believes that electronic privacy is essential for the ongoing success of the Internet as a service, whether it be a commercial medium or an entertainment medium. Our policy is to keep the personal information we receive from our sites completely confidential, and only use it solely for internal purposes. We will not share any of your personal information with any other parties. Please revisit our Privacy Policy from time to time to be sure that you are familiar with our current policy. Your continued use of DezineHub following any modifications to this Privacy Policy will be viewed as representing your acceptance of such changes. DezineHub will not disclose any individually identifiable information about its users to any third party. 

**Information Collected**  
When you register with DezineHub, our registration form requires you to give us your name, country, zip code/ postcode, and email address ("Registration Data"). Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. Generally, this information is collected through "traffic data" and may entail the use of "Cookies", "IP addresses" or other numeric codes used to identify a computer. 

**Use of Personal Information**  
DezineHub's primary aim in collecting personal information is to DezineHub also uses the personal information it collects to send its users e-mail notifications of any new features or services available through DezineHub, and other information that DezineHub feels might be of interest to it's users. In order to provide our users with a more personalized, relevant and intelligent service, DezineHub regularly makes improvements to the DezineHub site. The collection of personal data greatly assists DezineHub in making the necessary improvement in the site to cater for the specific interests and needs of the user’s of DezineHub. 

**Sharing Information**  
Except as set forth in the Terms of Use, DezineHub will not disclose personal data about you to any third parties without first receiving your permission. No personally identifiable data or information will be shared with advertisers or partners. Some of your information may be shared on an aggregate basis only, as a part of a larger set of statistics (for example, statistics that indicate the percentage of our members that are female), but that information will not be sufficient to permit the recipient to identify you. 

**Children**  
DezineHub does not intentionally collect or maintain information through Dezinehub.com from individuals actually known to be under the age of 13 ("children"). Moreover, at present, no part of Dezinehub.com is designed specifically to target or attract any children. Children should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to Dezinehub.com. 

**Other Sites**   
DezineHub contains links to other sites outside the DezineHub domains. DezineHub is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Additionally, if you make a purchase from a store or merchant listed on or linked to DezineHub, any information that you give, such as your credit card number and contact information, is provided to those merchants. These merchants have separate privacy and data collection practices and DezineHub has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies.
